

Federico Lupis

Software Developer

lupisfederico94@gmail.com

(+39) 393 33 48 258

Bari, Italy

drfede.github.io

linkedin.com/in/federico-lupis-78398316b in

github.com/https://gitlab.com/fedelup 🚺

Enthusiastic developer experienced in source code management (GIT and SubVersion), project management and issue tracking. Already experienced in teamwork (https://gitlab.com/fedelup94/globalgamejam and more) and used to work with tight deadlines. Good reading and writing skills in english. Keen on music and strategy games.

EDUCATION

Post Graduate Degree in Computer Game Development

Università degli Studi di Verona

10/2019 – Present

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science

Università degli Studi di Bari

09/2016 - 03/2020

High School

Liceo Scientifico Domenico Cirillo

2008 - 2013

Bari, Italy

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internet Assessor

Appen Limited

04/2019 - 08/2019

Italy

Internet Assessor

LionBridge Technologies, Inc

11/2018 – 04/2019

Italy

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Stranded (03/2020 - Present)

A twin-stick shooter/tower defense game, developed in Unity.

Remake (Global Game Jame 2020) (02/2020)

 A game about a man who has to destroy walls, developed in Unity.

Fruit Crash (01/2020)

A match-3 game developed in Unity

2D Game Engine (05/2019)

A simple game engine developed in C++ using SDL.

OTHER EXPERIENCES

Volunteer Experience (08/2019)

Volunteer at Sziget Festival (Hungary) as part of the recycling sensibilization team

CERTIFICATES

Certificate of completion of "Fundamentals of 2D Game Engines with C++ SDL and Lua" course (06/2019 – Present)

LANGUAGES

Italian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

VideoGames

New Technologies

Music